

PERSONAL INFORMATION

- Mobile 9337251737
- Total work experience
 15 Years 0 Month

CORE COMPETENCIES

SAP SD

KEY SKILLS

Marketing

Business Development

Channel Management

Key Accounts Management

Project Sales

Building Material

Sales

Budgeting And Forecasting

Sujeet Mohapatra

Deputy Regional Manager
 Sales and Marketing

56

MBA/PGDM (Marketing And Finance), Seeking Zonal or Regional Assignment In Sales And Distribution Management And Business Development With An Organization Of High Repute. Handling Team Of 26 On Roll Employees in Jharkhand & Odisha

PROFILE SUMMARY

15 Years of experience in Building Materials - Plumbing ,Drainage, Agriculture & Focus Product both in Channel and Project Sales,Telecom Channel Sales and FMCG Distribution Sales Have good understanding of business processes in Sales and Distribution Management. Heading Odisha & Jharkhand in current organisation for more than 10 years. Managing a team of 26 On Roll Employees. Knowledge in SAP SD Module.

EDUCATION

2008	MBA/PGDM Institute of Chartered Financial Analysts of India (ICFAI)
2001	B.Com Utkal University
1998	XIIth English
1996	Xth Oriya

WORK EXPERIENCE

OTHER PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth 15-May-1981

Gender Male

Address AT/P.O.- Kalyani

Nagar,Behind Vigilance Colony,

Odisha

City Bhubaneswar

Country INDIA

Marital Married

Status

Apr 2019 -Present Deputy Regional Manager - Sales and Marketing

Astral Limited

Handling a team of 26 onroll employees in Distribution Channel & Project. Significant Presence at Dealer, Plumber, Architect, Promoter, Plumbing Contractor & Consultant level across |harkhand & Odisha

Apr 2016 -Mar 2019 Assistant Regional Manager - Sales and Marketing

Astral Limited

Handling a team of 9 onroll employees, Distribution Channel & Project both Govt and Private & Presence at Architects, Builders, Plumbing Contractors & Consultants Across Jharkhand & Odisha

Aug 2012 -Mar 2016 Area Manager - Sales and Marketing

Astral Limited

Company Overview: Astral Limited is the first to manufacture and market the most advanced CPVC Pro plumbing system for the first time in India. Astral was established in 1999 with a single minded purpose to manufacture the best plumbing system in India. Astral has incorporate latest technology and quality control programs which are widely accepted at global level. Job Profile: . Identify new business opportunities in the entire region. . To provide technical support to the dealers. . Implement sales strategies to budget sales & collection targets. . To follow up with dealers for payments & sales. . Market analysis & new application development.

Sep 2010 - Ju^Q 2012 Head of Sales

The ROOF

Sales Team Management, Customer Care Team Management, Tie Up With Promoters Aug 2009 -Aug 2010

Senior Territory Manager - Sales and Distribution

Unitech Wireless East Private Limited

Company Overview: Uninor is a mobile telephony and network operator in India. Uninor is subsidiary of Norwegian telecom giant Telenor Group (67.25%) and Unitech Group (32.75%). Uninor has started mobile services in India at the end of 2009, focusing on the GSM technology. Telenor is having its existence in 14 countries worldwide. Job Profile: Handling Channel sales- 3 Distributors, 4 KAMs, 14 RSEs,5 Promoters, 5 Merchandisers, 3 MIS. Revenue generation. New customer addition. Selling of different VAS (Value Added Services). Retention of existing customers and Strengthen the distribution through retailers. Increase the utilization of every tower under assigned territory. Existence of visibility of our product in the market through banners, posters, danglers, hoarding, in shop branding.

Oct 2008 - Jul 2009 Territory Manager

Dishnet Wireless Limited - Sales and Distribution

Company Overview: The Aircel Group, formed in 1994, offers affordable and outstanding mobile services to a vast subscriber base of 51.83 millions in India. Aircel is a joint venture between Maxis Communications of Malaysia and the Reddy family of Chennai. Maxis has a 74% stake in Aircel and the remaining 26% is with Sindya Securities & Investments Private Limited. Now Aircel operates in 23 telecom circles. Job Profile: Handling 4 distributors/ 10 Rural distributors in Cuttack & Outskirt of Cuttack. Handling a team of 2 Territory Managers, 3 PSRs and 10 sales executives. Responsible for primary, secondary sales of RCVs, sim selling and activations. Expansion of new outlet, activating outlet, transacting outlet. Achieved 100% target in Cuttack urban in October 2008 and 170% target in Cuttack rural in the month of November and December 2008.

Mar 2008 -Sep 2008

Territory Sales Officer - Sales and Distribution

Anmol Biscuit Limited

Company Overview: Anmol is a popular brand of eastern & northern region of India. Anmol Biscuits one of the leading biscuit manufacturer of the country having its two state of the art units at West Bengal & Noida. Anmol is one of the largest brands across the country having 110 Super stockists, 2600 distributors & 250 sales person & present in about more than 4 lakhs retail shop. Job Profile Managing the marketing operation in the assigned territory of Cuttack. Achieving the target of 6000 cartoons worth Rs 18 Lacs per month. Appointed two new distributors as per beat plan. Looking after the primary selling, secondary selling and collection etc. Feedback on customer requirements with respect to new products.